exportpages.com 2017-09-04

# Privacy Policy

This website is operated by Exportpages International GmbH, Am Borsigturm 31, 13507 Berlin, Germany (Exportpages). We operate a number of websites, some of which give you an opportunity to register or provide us with personal information about yourself. 

Important information 

Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy: 

  * We do not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes 
  * We do not share your contact information with another User without your consent 
  * Any personally identifiable information that you provide will be secured with industry standard protocols and technology 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. By continuing to use the Exportpages service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on the Exportpages website, you are consenting to the changes. 

Please read this privacy policy to learn more about: 

Registration 

In order to become a User, you must first create an account on our website. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information, which you recognize and expressly acknowledge is personal information allowing others, including Exportpages, to identify you: name, email address, country, ZIP/postal code, a brief summary of your company, and a password chosen by you. 

Customer Service 

Exportpages may collect information through the Exportpages website in order to, among other things, accurately categorize and respond to a customer’s inquiry and deliver appropriate service levels. 

Google Analytics 

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. In case of activation of the IP anonymization, Google will truncate/anonymize the last octet of the IP address for Member States of the European Union as well as for other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases, the full IP address is sent to and shortened by Google servers in the USA. On behalf of the website provider Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage to the website provider. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. Furthermore you can prevent Google’s collection and use of data (cookies and IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB.

Cookies 

Like most websites, Exportpages uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows Exportpages to recognize you as a User when you return to the Exportpages website using the same computer and web browser. If your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use the Exportpages website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on our website. 

One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you’ve logged in to your Exportpages account. The next time you visit the Exportpages website, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing User so you will not need to log in before using the service. In order to access or change any of your private information (like a credit card number) or to send a message to another User, however, you must log in securely again with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie. 

Additionally, if you log out of the Exportpages website you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Exportpages website. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser. 

We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing User preferences and tracking User trends. In the course of serving advertisements or optimizing services to our Users, we may allow authorized third parties to place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Any information provided to third parties through such cookies will not be personally identifiable but may provide general segment information, e.g. your industry or geographic location, your occupation, or information about your professional or educational background, for greater customization of your user experience. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies or you opt to refuse all cookies, you may not be able to use the Exportpages website or services. Exportpages does not store personally identifiable information in the cookies. 

Uses of personal information 

Exportpages is an online service dedicated to helping all types of professionals more effectively connect with one another. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on our website is used to help you describe yourself to other Users. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by Exportpages from Users and is exclusively owned by Exportpages. This information can be utilized by Exportpages in such manner as Exportpages, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate. 

Sharing Information with Third Parties 

We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable information with third parties to carry out your instructions or to provide specific services or information. For instance, we use a credit card processing company to bill Users for subscription fees. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and they are bound by confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information. 

Security 

In order to secure your personal information, access to your data on Exportpages is password-protected, and sensitive data is protected by SSL encryption when it is exchanged between your web browser and the Exportpages web site. To protect any data you store on our servers we also regularly audit our system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks and we use a tier-one secured-access data center. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information. Please note that emails and similar means of communication with other users of Exportpages are not encrypted and we strongly request you not to communicate any confidential information through these means. 

Legal Disclaimer 

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, such as responses to civil or criminal subpoenas, or other requests by law enforcement personnel. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, subpoena, or other legal process or request to Exportpages brought in any country throughout the world, or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

How to contact us 

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at [support@exportpages.com](mailto:support@exportpages.com) or contact us at: 

Exportpages International GmbH  
Attn: Privacy Policy  
Kurfürstendamm 11  
10719 Berlin   
Germany
